?THEME SONG: Are you ready kids
主题曲：孩子们准备好了吗
!Aye, aye, Captain
！是啊是啊，队长
!I can't hear you
！我听不到你说话
!Aye, aye, Captain
！是啊是啊，队长
!Ohhhhhhhhhh
！哦哦哦哦哦
Who lives in a
?pineapple under the sea
谁住在一个
?海底菠萝
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
Absorbent and yellow
!and porous is he
吸水性和黄色
！他是多孔的
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
If nautical nonsense
be something
如果航海废话
成为某物
you wish-- SpongeBob
!Squarepants
你所希望的——海绵宝宝
!方裤
Then drop on the deck
!and float like a fish
然后落在甲板上
！像鱼一样漂浮
!SpongeBob Squarepants
!海绵宝宝
?Ready
？准备好
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
!SpongeBob Squarepants
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
!Ha-ha
！哈哈
!Ha-ha-ha-ha
！哈哈哈哈哈哈
!Ah-ha
！啊哈
!Har
！哈尔
[DIXIELAND JAZZ PLAYING]
[迪克西兰爵士乐演奏]
All right, we're going-
!to go to Sandy's house
好吧，我们要去——
!去桑迪家
!Yeah
！是的
!Oh, it's going to be fun-
！哦，这会很有趣-
?Sandy-
？沙-
!Hey, Sandy
！嘿，桑迪
?What's with the sign
?这个标志是怎么回事
.Look-
。看-
.She's on the Eating Channel
.她在饮食频道
[CRUNCHING]
[嘎吱嘎吱]
[GULP]
[咕噜咕噜]
.Howdy-
.你好-
If you all are
watching this, that
如果你们都是
看着这个那个
.means I'm asleep for the winter
.意味着我在冬天睡觉
This sleep is called
".hibernation"
这种睡眠称为
“.冬眠”
[MUNCHING SOUNDS]
[咀嚼声]
During hibernation, animals
.don't like to be woken up
动物在冬眠期间
.不喜欢被吵醒
.So, do not disturb
.所以，请勿打扰
.That means you, SpongeBob
.那就是你，海绵宝宝
.We'd better put these on-
.我们最好把这些-
.Never mind, Pat-
.没关系，帕特-
.Sandy said not to come in
.桑迪说不要进来
!Let's amscray
！让我们来吧
When are you going-
?to learn, SpongeBob
你什么时候去——
？学习，海绵宝宝
".No" means "yes"
“.No”的意思是“是”
.Patrick-
.帕特里克-
.Listen
。听
--How many times do we have to
——我们还要经历多少次
!SpongeBob-
！海绵宝宝-
!Look at this
！看这个
[GASPS]
[喘气]
?What is this stuff-
？这是什么东西-
It's a vast swirling wonderland-
.of sparkling white pleasure
这是一片广阔的旋转仙境——
.闪闪发光的白色快乐
Let it fill your senses with
cascading fluffy pillows
让它充满你的感官
层叠的蓬松枕头
of excitement and comfort
!as you've never felt before
的兴奋和安慰
!就像你以前从未感受过的那样
.Wow, Patrick-
.哇，帕特里克-
!That was beautiful
！那真是太美了
?What-
？什么-
I was just reading
.this candy wrapper
我刚刚在读书
.这个糖果包装纸
?See
？看
[GASP]
[喘气]
!Patrick-
！帕特里克-
!Put your helmet back on
！重新戴上头盔
You know there's no
!water at Sandy's house
你知道没有
！桑迪家的水
.It's OK, SpongeBob-
.没关系，海绵宝宝-
.This stuff is water
.这东西是水
!Look
！看
.I guess you're right-
.我想你是对的-
.It's OK here
.这里没问题
.Take it off-
.脱下来-
.No one's looking
.没人看
!TOGETHER: Yeah
！一起：是的
!Yeah
！是的
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
?SpongeBob-
？海绵宝宝-
?Did you hear that
？你听到了吗
I think it came from-
.up in Sandy's tree
我认为它来自——
.在桑迪的树上
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
.That is one tired tree-
.那是一棵疲惫的树-
[GASP]
[喘气]
.Look what's in Sandy's bed-
.看看桑迪的床上有什么-
It looks like an-
.over-inflated Sandy doll
它看起来像一个——
.过度充气的桑迪娃娃
.I think this thing is Sandy-
.我认为这个东西是桑迪-
Hibernation" must mean the"-
".opposite of "beauty sleep
冬眠”一定是指“——
“.与”美容觉相反
I've had enough of your-
.dastardly deeds, Dirty Dan
我已经受够你了——
.卑鄙的行为，肮脏的丹
I'm going to get you and
,your partner, Pinhead Larry
我会去找你并且
，你的搭档，针头拉里
.or my name ain't Sheriff Sandy
.或者我的名字不是桑迪警长
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
She must be dreaming-
.about Texas outlaws
她一定是在做梦——
.关于德克萨斯亡命之徒
[SNICKERING]
[窃笑]
.Look out Sandy
.注意桑迪
.I'm Dirty Dan
.我是肮脏的丹
I'm gonna catch-
you and throw you
我要抓住-
你然后扔你
.and Dale at taxpayers' expense
.和戴尔由纳税人承担费用
Ooh, you'd better-
.run faster, Sandy
哦，你最好-
.跑得更快，桑迪
.Yeah, I'm getting away-
.是的，我要走了-
!Run faster
！跑得更快
!Hurry-
！匆忙-
!We're getting in a taxi
！我们要坐出租车了
!Faster-
！快点-
!Faster
！快点
.I'll get you two-
.我会给你两个-
--You're nothing but pure evil
.just like the newspaper comics
——你只不过是纯粹的邪恶
.就像报纸漫画一样
[SNICKERING]
[窃笑]
.Come on Patrick-
.来吧帕特里克-
We shouldn't
.disturb her anymore
我们不应该
.别再打扰她了
.That's not disturbing-
.这并不令人不安-
.This is disturbing
.这令人不安
.Hi there, SpongeBob
.你好，海绵宝宝
!My name is Patback
！我的名字是帕特贝克
!Ha
！哈
!That is really disturbing
！这真是令人不安
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
.Oh, SpongeBob-
.哦，海绵宝宝-
[GROWL]
[咆哮]
[ROAR]
[吼]
!Faster, SpongeBob-
！快一点，海绵宝宝-
!She's gaining on us
！她正在追上我们
!Sandy-
！沙-
!No
！不
!Stop
！停止
!I warned ya, Dirty Dan-
！我警告过你，肮脏的丹-
Now you just crossed the
.border into Hurtville
现在你刚刚跨过
.边境进入赫特维尔
!Sandy-
！沙-
!It's us
！是我们
!Your friends
！你的朋友
!SpongeBob and Patrick
！海绵宝宝和帕特里克
!Please, Sandy-
！拜托，桑迪-
!I can't afford dry-cleaning
！我付不起干洗费用
Gonna skin ya and make-
.a pair of size six boots
要去剥你的皮然后做——
.一双六号靴子
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
.Fun's over-
.乐趣结束了-
.Whew-
.呼-
We sure don't want
.to wake her up again
我们当然不想要
.再次叫醒她
Too bad we don't have any
.ear plugs to put on her
可惜我们没有
.给她戴上耳塞
.Yeah-
。是的-
All's I got is this
.belly-button lint
我所拥有的就是这个
.肚脐绒毛
!All right, Pat-
！好吧，帕特——
I'm gonna rip your arms-
.off-- and flapjacks
我要撕断你的手臂——
.off-- 和烙饼
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
.Well, that outta work-
.好吧，那不工作了-
!Hey Sandy-
！嘿桑迪-
?Does it work
?有效吗
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
.Hey Sandy-
.嘿桑迪-
,If you can't hear us
!don't say anything
,如果你听不到我们的声音
！什么也别说
!Hey, Sandy-
！嘿，桑迪-
!Don't wake up
！别醒来
[GIGGLING]
[咯咯笑]
!See you later, Sheriff Sandy-
！再见，桑迪警长——
!Ba-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
！巴哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
!You're under arrest
！你被捕了
!You'll never catch me-
！你永远抓不到我-
!Da-
！哒——
!Ha-ha-ha-
！哈哈哈哈-
!Oo
！哦
!Ba-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-
！巴哈哈哈哈哈哈哈——
!Hey, that's not fair-
！嘿，这不公平-
.Cowboys couldn't afford canons
.牛仔买不起大炮
They couldn't afford-
.station waggons, either
他们买不起——
.旅行车，或者
.Nice panelling-
.漂亮的镶板-
,All right, Pinhead
.your time is up
，好吧，针头
.你的时间到了
?Who are you calling Pinhead-
？你叫谁针头-
.I want to be Dirty Dan
.我想成为肮脏的丹
What makes you think-
?you can be Dirty Dan
是什么让你想到——
？你可以成为肮脏的丹
.I'm dirty-
.我很脏-
.I'd say I'm Dirty Dan-
.我会说我是肮脏的丹-
!Dow-
！陶氏-
!Oof-
！钱币-
.I'd say I'm Dirty Dan-
.我会说我是肮脏的丹-
!Dow
！陶氏
!I'm Dirty Dan-
！我是肮脏的丹-
!Oof
！钱币
!I'm Dirty Dan-
！我是肮脏的丹-
!Doh
！多哦
!PATRICK: I'm Dirty Dan
！帕特里克：我是肮脏的丹
!SPONGEBOB: I'm Dirty Dan
!海绵宝宝：我是肮脏的丹
.PATRICK: I'm Dirty Dan
.PATRICK：我是肮脏的丹
!SPONGEBOB: I'm Dirty Dan
!海绵宝宝：我是肮脏的丹
!Oh
！哦
!I'm Dirty Dan-
！我是肮脏的丹-
!Auugh-
！啊——
--Screaming will get you no-
——尖叫不会让你受伤——
Which one of you fellers-
?is the real Dirty Dan
你们哪一个家伙——
？才是真正的肮脏丹
?Uh-
？呃-
?I am
？我是
!Patrick-
！帕特里克-
.Hot wings-
.热翅-
.OK, Pinhead Larry-
.好吧，笨蛋拉里-
!Now you get yours
！现在你得到你的了
!Auugh-
！啊——
!Pinhead-
！针头-
[GASPING FOR BREATH]
[喘气]
Now you're gonna pay for
!those crimes, Pinhead
现在你要付出代价
！那些罪行，Pinhead
!Sandy-
！沙-
!Stand back
！退后一步
!I'm warning you
！我警告你
[ROARS]
[咆哮]
!OK-
！好的-
!I warned ya
！我警告过你
!Uh
！呃
?Did you win-
？你赢了吗-
!Hi, SpongeBob
！嗨，海绵宝宝
[SNORING SOUNDS]
[鼾声]
.OK, SpongeBob
.好吧，海绵宝宝
.You can be Dirty Dan
.你可以成为肮脏的丹
.I just want to be Patrick
.我只想成为帕特里克
Let's get out of here-
!before Sandy wakes up again
我们离开这里吧——
！在桑迪再次醒来之前
[GASPING FOR BREATH]
[喘气]
.Ouch
。哎哟
Sorry, Patrick, but
.the door is slippery
抱歉，帕特里克，但是
.门很滑
!It's frozen shut
！它被冻住了
.Let me have a try-
.让我尝试一下-
!Tuh
！呃
!Open sesame
！芝麻开门
.Well, I've done all I can do
.好吧，我已经做了我能做的一切
,Then we're stuck in here-
.until the door thaws
，然后我们就被困在这里了-
.直到门解冻
.In spring
.春天
!Barnacles-
！藤壶-
[SHIVERING]
[颤抖]
?Is it spring, yet
?春天还没到吗
.N-N-N-no-
.N-N-N-无-
!Oh-
！哦-
!I'm so cold that I'm shivering
！我冷得发抖
I-I-I'm so cold-
that can use my nose
我-我-我好冷-
可以用我的鼻子
drippings as a
.pair of chopsticks
滴水作为
.一双筷子
I'm so c-cold-
!that I'm shivering
我好冷-
！我在发抖
M-m-m-maybe we-
?should build a fire
嗯-嗯-也许我们-
？应该生火
.I got it
。我得到了它
We'll burn the bark
!from Sandy's tree
我们会烧掉树皮
！来自桑迪的树
SANDY SQUIRREL: You're going
to be wearing an iron lung
桑迪松鼠：你要去
戴着铁肺
when I'm through
!with you, Pinhead
当我结束时
！和你在一起，针头
That fire's not going-
.to happen, Patrick
那火不会熄灭——
.发生了，帕特里克
.I don't get it
.我不明白
How does Sandy survive these
?intense conditions every year
桑迪如何度过这些难关
？每年的恶劣条件
.Maybe she just ignores it-
.也许她只是忽略了它-
--Maybe-
- 或许-
!Maybe it's her fur-
！也许是她的毛皮——
[SQUIRREL SOUND]
[松鼠的声音]
!TOGETHER: Yeah
！一起：是的
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
Look at all that-
.warm, toasty fur
看看这一切——
.温暖、烘烤的皮毛
--It's like a goldmine-
!but with fur
——就像一座金矿——
！但有毛皮
.Carefully-
。小心-
!Carefully
！小心
!Come on-
！快点-
!Do it
！做吧
!I'm freezing here
!All right-
！我这里冻僵了
！好吧-
!All right
！好的
!Hang on a second
！等一下
[ROAR]
[吼]
?That should be enough, right
？应该够了吧
.Sponge-
。海绵-
.I'm a big man
.我是个大男人
A big, big man
一个很大很大的男人
Well I guess I've-
.lived a full life
好吧，我想我已经-
.过着充实的生活
[ROAR]
[吼]
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
.This is taking too long-
.这花了太长时间-
!I want the warm now
！我现在就想要温暖
!Pat, no-
！帕特，不——
?Pat, are you crazy
？帕特，你疯了吗
.No-
。不-
.I'm warm
.我很温暖
.Let me see that roll of tape-
.让我看看那卷胶带-
[ROAR]
[吼]
[TAPE RIP]
[胶带撕裂]
[ROAR]
[吼]
[TAPE RIP]
[胶带撕裂]
[ROAR]
[吼]
[TAPE RIP]
[胶带撕裂]
[ROAR]
[吼]
[TAPE RIP]
[胶带撕裂]
[ROAR]
[吼]
.Man-
。男人-
.That fur really hits the spot
.那皮毛真的很合适
.No more frozen armpits
.不再有冰冻的腋窝
And this eyebrow goatee
.combo works like a charm
还有这眉毛山羊胡子
.combo 很有魅力
This is the best
.idea we've ever had
这是最好的
.我们曾经有过的想法
.You said it-
.你说过-
,I'm ready for the longest-
!coldest winter ever
,我已经做好了最长的准备-
！有史以来最冷的冬天
!TOGETHER: Bring it on
!一起：加油
?Spring-
？春天-
!SANDY SQUIRREL: Yawn
!桑迪松鼠：打哈欠
!Wow
！哇
!Spring already
！春天已经来了
[GASPING FOR BREATH]
[喘气]
!Tartar sauce-
!塔塔酱-
!The lock is still frozen
！锁仍然被冻结
I sure can't wait to get-
!outside and warm my fur
我肯定等不及想要-
！到外面来温暖我的毛皮
[HUFFING AND PUFFING]
[气喘吁吁]
!Oh, look
！哦，看
!It's SpongeBob and Patrick
！这是海绵宝宝和帕特里克
!Hey guys
！嘿伙计们
[SHRIEKS]
[尖叫声]
.It's OK, Sandy-
.没关系，桑迪-
Squirrel-pattern baldness is
.quite common in small mammals
松鼠型秃发是
.在小型哺乳动物中很常见
!SpongeBob-
！海绵宝宝-
!Patrick
！帕特里克
.Don't worry Sandy
.别担心桑迪
!We've got you covered
！我们为您服务
?More lemonade, boys-
？再来点柠檬水，孩子们——
.Thanks, Sandy-
.谢谢，桑迪-
!Spring sure is lovely-
！春天真是可爱啊-
[SAD PIANO MUSIC]
[悲伤的钢琴音乐]
[GIGGLING]
[咯咯笑]
.Oh, I've got you now, Gary-
.哦，我现在找到你了，加里-
.Meow-
.喵-
!Tag-
！标签-
!You're it
！就是你了
!Da-ha-ha-ha-ha
！哈哈哈哈哈哈
!Gary-
！加里-
!You will never find me here
！你永远不会在这里找到我
!Oh-oh
！哦哦
.Meow-
.喵-
.Tag-
。标签-
.Now I'm it
.现在我就是了
!Da-ha-ha-ha-ha
！哈哈哈哈哈哈
.Hi, SpongeBob-
.嗨，海绵宝宝-
?What are you doing
？你在干什么
.Gary and I are playing tag-
.加里和我正在玩捉迷藏-
?You want to join us
?你想加入我们
?Oh, boy, would I-
？哦，孩子，我会-
.OK-
。好的-
.Tag
。标签
!You're it
！就是你了
!I'm it-
！我就是——
!I'm it
！我就是它
.Meow-
.喵-
!Tag, you're it-
！标签，就是你——
!I win
！我赢了
[PURRING]
[咕噜声]
?What's with Gary
?加里怎么了
.He sounds like a motorboat
.他听起来像一艘摩托艇
Must be the snail's way-
.of saying he likes you
一定是蜗牛的方式——
.说他喜欢你
!Ha-ha-
！哈哈-
!It tickles
！好痒啊
[LAUGHING TOGETHER]
[一起笑]
[STILL LAUGHING TOGETHER]
[仍然一起笑]
.Well-
。出色地-
I guess it's time for me and
.the Gar-bear to get going
我想现在是我和
.加熊出发
.Come on, Gary
.来吧，加里
Boy, I can't wait
.to hit the hay
男孩，我等不及了
. 去干草
?How about you, Gary
？你呢，加里
?Gary
？加里
.SINGING) Brush brush brush)-
.SINGING）刷刷刷）-
.Brush brush brush
.刷刷刷
?Hey Patrick-
？嘿帕特里克-
?Have you seen Gary
？你见过加里吗？
.Brush brush brush-
.刷刷刷-
!Brushing everywhere
！到处刷
.Nope
。没有
.Oh
。哦
.I-- hey, here he is
.我--嘿，他在这里
.Meow-
.喵-
.Come on Gary-
.来吧，加里-
We've gotta let
.Patrick go to sleep
我们必须让
.帕特里克去睡觉
.Oh, I don't mind, SpongeBob-
.哦，我不介意，海绵宝宝-
In fact, why don't you let Gary
?sleep over at my house tonight
事实上，你为什么不让加里
？今晚在我家过夜
!Hey, that's a great idea-
！嘿，这是个好主意-
!A sleepover-
！过夜-
!Oh boy
！天哪
Oh, this is going
!to be great, Gary
哦，这是要
！要变得伟大，加里
We can stay up till dawn
,and watch scary movies
我们可以熬夜到天亮
以及看恐怖电影
,and eat popcorn
!and play boardgames
,然后吃爆米花
！并玩棋盘游戏
.Gee-
.哎呀-
.This is great
.这太棒了
My two best friends in the
!whole sea having a sleepover
我在这两个最好的朋友
！整个大海都在过夜
And then we'll make-
!a house of cards
然后我们将-
！纸牌屋
And then we'll read
!some comic books
然后我们会读到
！一些漫画书
.OK-
。好的-
.You guys have a good time
.你们玩得很开心
.I'll see you tomorrow
.明天见
!Bla-bla-bla-bla-blah-
！啦啦啦啦啦啦啦-
!Bla-bla
！啦啦啦
[SHIP HORN]
[船喇叭]
!I'm awake-
！我醒了——
!Hey, SpongeBob-
！嘿，海绵宝宝-
!Hey guys-
！嘿伙计们-
?How was the sleepover
？过夜怎么样？
.Great, SpongeBob-
.太棒了，海绵宝宝-
!Watch this
！看这个
No matter where I
.go, Gary follows
无论我在哪里
.go，加里跟随
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
!Meow-
!喵-
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
.Meow-
.喵-
?See-
？看-
.Come on, Gary-
.来吧，加里-
!Try and catch me
！尝试抓住我
!Da-ha-ha-ha-ha
！哈哈哈哈哈哈
?Isn't this great, Gary
？这不是很棒吗，加里
Me running around
!and you chasing me
到处乱跑的我
！而你在追我
.You're not chasing me
.你没有追我
.Come on, Gary-
.来吧，加里-
.Let's go play a different game
.我们去玩别的游戏吧
!Whoa-ho-ho-ho-
！哇-嗬-嗬-嗬-
!Look out
！当心
.I'm right in front of-- you
.我就在——你的面前
?What's wrong with me
？我怎么了
?Do I offend
？我冒犯了吗
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
!Hey, Gary
！嘿，加里
!Gary, look
！加里，看
!It's your favourite ball
！这是你最喜欢的球
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
!Hey, Gary-
！嘿，加里-
!Look
！看
!Snail Nip
!蜗牛咬
?Huh
？哈
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
!Oh-
！哦-
!Gary, help
！加里，救命
!Help me
！帮我
!Oh, merciful Neptune
！哦，仁慈的海王星
!I closed the window on my head
！我关上了头上的窗户
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
.All right
。好的
!That's it
！就是这样
!Da
！达
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
!Gary
！加里
You stop this
!foolishness right now
你停止这个
！现在的愚蠢
.Gary the snail
.蜗牛加里
Answer me when I'm
!talking to you
当我在的时候回答我
!在跟你说话
.OK
。好的
!That's it, mister
！就是这样，先生
you are coming home with
.me right this instant
你回家时带着
.我现在就对了
.Say goodbye to Patrick, Gary
.向帕特里克、加里说再见
!Meow-
!喵-
Hold it right there-
!DadMom AngryPants
就这样握着吧——
！爸爸妈妈生气了
?What's that supposed to mean-
？那是什么意思-
.I don't know-
。我不知道-
But I do know Gary knows
.who he wants to go with
但我知道加里知道
.他想和谁一起去
Now I suggest you put him
.down and let him choose
现在我建议你把他
.down 让他选择
.Fine-
。美好的-
But I would like to
remind him who it was that
但我想
提醒他那是谁
,fed him and housed him
and sat at his bedside
，喂养他并安置他
坐在他的床边
when he was sick, and
massaged his eyestalks
当他生病时，以及
按摩他的眼柄
!when his eyes were sore
！当他的眼睛酸痛的时候
.OK, Gary
.好的，加里
.Go ahead
。前进
.Show him
.给他看
.OK Gary
.好的加里
!Come to me
！到我这里来
!Come on
！快点
!Come on, Gary
！来吧，加里
.Come on
。快点
.Come here, Gary
.过来，加里
.Oh, wrong way, Gary
.哦，走错了，加里
!G-Gary
!G-加里
!Turn around, Gary
！转过身来，加里
!Turn around
！回转
!G-Gary, no
！G-加里，不
!Gary, no
！加里，不
!No, no, no, no
！不，不，不，不
!Don't do it Gary
！别这样做，加里
!No
！不
!No, Gary
！不，加里
.Well, well, well-
.好吧，好吧，好吧-
I guess that answers
.that question
我想这就是答案
.那个问题
.So long, SpongeBob
.再见，海绵宝宝
.Gary and me got stuff to do
.加里和我有事要做
.OK, fine-
.好吧，好吧-
If that's the way
you want to thank
如果是这样的话
你想感谢
!me for all that I've done
！感谢我所做的一切
I guess you're not
.coming back, Gary
我猜你不是
.回来了，加里
.I don't need Gary
.我不需要加里
.I'll just find another pet
.我会再找一只宠物
!Yeah, it'll be better than Gary
！是的，它会比加里更好
I'm going to get a pet who won't
!go off with my best friend
我要养一只不会的宠物
！和我最好的朋友一起走吧
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
!Hi, guys
！嗨，大家好
.Say hello to my new pal, Rex
.向我的新朋友雷克斯问好
!Woof-
！纬-
,Not only is he loyal-
.but he knows tricks, too
,他不仅忠诚——
.但他也知道技巧
.Watch and learn
.观看和学习
!Sit, Rex
！坐下，雷克斯
!Sit
！坐
!Roll over, Rex
！翻滚，雷克斯
!Roll over
！滚下
.Now stay, Rex
.现在留下来，雷克斯
!Stay
！停留
!Good boy, Rex
！好孩子，雷克斯
?Who's a good boy
?谁是好孩子
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
I'm sure glad we went
.our separate ways, Gary
我很高兴我们去了
.我们分道扬镳，加里
.A worm really is the pet for me
.蠕虫真的是我的宠物
.So loyal
.如此忠诚
.So trusting
.如此信任
.Always by my side
.永远在我身边
!Woof-
！纬-
?Who needs worms, anyway-
？无论如何，谁需要蠕虫-
,Welcome home
.newest best friend
,欢迎回家
.最新最好的朋友
.Come on out
.出来吧
.Don't be shy
.别害羞
!Ooh hoo
！哦呼
You remind me of
.someone I once knew
你让我想起
.我曾经认识的人
A certain someone
who's name will not
某个人
谁的名字不会
.be mentioned in this household
.在这个家庭中被提及
!Come on
！快点
.Let me show you around, Larry
.让我带你四处看看，拉里
.Meow-
.喵-
And now, Larry, I present-
!to you-- dinner time
现在，拉里，我提出——
!致你——晚餐时间
!Ta-da
！田田
!Bon appetit, Larry
！祝你胃口好，拉里
[SNIFFING]
[嗅探]
[HISSING]
[嘶嘶声]
.OK-
。好的-
.Maybe later
.也许稍后
.This is where you sleep, Larry
.这就是你睡觉的地方，拉里
!Rawr-
！拉尔-
--Uh, that's where I-
——呃，那是我——
[HISSING]
[嘶嘶声]
[SNORING]
[打鼾]
.I guess you can sleep there
.我想你可以睡在那里
.I'll sleep down here
.我会睡在这里
.Well, goodnight, Larry
.好吧，晚安，拉里
[HISSING]
[嘶嘶声]
!Hey-hey, Larry-
！嘿嘿，拉里-
?Want to hear a joke
？想听个笑话
.Oh, Gary used to love this one
.哦，加里以前很喜欢这个
What do you call
?a snail on a ship
你叫什么
？船上的蜗牛
!A snailer
！一只蜗牛
!Da-ha-ha-ha-ha
！哈哈哈哈哈哈
[HISSING]
[嘶嘶声]
?Don't you get it, Larry-
？你不明白吗，拉里-
!A snailer
！一只蜗牛
.Gosh
.天啊
Larry sure is
.different than Gary
拉里肯定是
.与加里不同
And Gary and Larry are
.real different than Jerry
加里和拉里是
.和杰瑞真的不一样
!Oh, Gary
！哦，加里
?Why did you have to go
？你为什么要走
?Why, Gary
？为什么，加里
?Why
？为什么
,Why, why, why
?why, why, why, why
、为什么、为什么、为什么
？为什么，为什么，为什么，为什么
.GARY: Meow
.GARY：喵
?Huh-
？哈-
?Gary
？加里
.Hey, SpongeBob-
.嘿，海绵宝宝-
.Oh-
。哦-
.Hello, Patrick
.你好，帕特里克
.Meow-
.喵-
.Hello, Gary-
.你好，加里-
Would it be all-
right if Gary and I
难道这一切都是——
如果加里和我就对了
?did some laundry over here
？在这里洗了一些衣服
?Laundry-
？洗衣店-
.But we used to do laundry
.但我们以前经常洗衣服
,PATRICK: And uh, SpongeBob
?could we borrow some soap
帕特里克：呃，海绵宝宝
？我们可以借点肥皂吗
?Soap-
？肥皂-
.But we used to use soap
.但是我们以前用肥皂
Do you want Fresh
--Scent or Heavy Du
你想要新鲜吗
--气味或重度
.Here it comes-
.来了——
!Du-- du-- du-- duty-
！杜--杜--杜--职责-
!Gary
！加里
!Please come back Gary
！请回来，加里
!Please come home
！请回家吧
!I'm a wreck without you
！没有你我​​就一塌糊涂
!I know
！我知道
If you come back, there
!will be a no rules rule
如果你回来的话，那里
！将是一个无规则的规则
You can do whatever you
!want, when you want
你可以做任何你想做的事
！想要，当你想要的时候
If you feel like ripping up
!the sofa, then you rip it up
如果你想撕碎
！沙发，然后你把它撕碎
?And the litter box
？还有垃圾箱
!Forget about it
！忘了它吧
!The world is your litter box
！世界就是你的垃圾箱
And you don't have
to wait around for me
而你没有
等我
.to feed you anymore
.不再喂你了
.24 hour fridge access
.24小时冰箱使用
And you don't even if have to
!use a bowl-- blub-blub-blub
即使有必要你也不需要
！用碗——blub-blub-blub
And I know how much
you like my prize
我知道多少
你喜欢我的奖品
.driftwood carving of Squidward
.章鱼哥的浮木雕刻
Well, think of it as your
.own personal scratching post
好吧，把它当作你的
.自己的个人抓痕帖子
?What do you think, Gary
？你觉得怎么样，加里
?Won't it be fun, Gary
？这不是很有趣吗，加里
!How pathetic-
！多么可悲啊——
!Gary-
！加里-
,I'm sorry, SpongeBob-
.but Gary's with me, now
，对不起，海绵宝宝-
.但是现在加里和我在一起
,You had your chance
.and you failed
,你有机会
.而你失败了
You have to stop
.living in the past
你必须停下来
.生活在过去
.Face it, SpongeBob
.面对现实吧，海绵宝宝
.You're only hurting yourself
.你只是在伤害你自己
.It's what Gary wants
.这就是加里想要的
.And what Gary wants is me
.加里想要的是我
?Right, Gary
？对了，加里
?Huh
？哈
[MUNCHING SOUNDS]
[咀嚼声]
!He only liked me for my shorts
！他只喜欢我的短裤
.No, Patrick-
.不，帕特里克-
He wanted the cookie
!in your pocket
他想要饼干
！在你的口袋里
.Meow-
.喵-
?G-- G-- Gary-
？G-- G-- 加里-
.Burp-
.打嗝-
!Meow
！喵
!Wee-
！威-
!Oh, Gary
！哦，加里
!I knew you'd never leave me
！我就知道你永远不会离开我
!Aw
！噢
!Let's go for a walk, pal
！我们去散步吧，朋友
!Gary-
！加里-
I thought what we
!had was special
我以为我们
!有很特别
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]